{
    "id": "8166b1be577847ad88777ff02836aa20",
    "title": "Too, So, And Enough",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d1498b363354479aa5aff9cb4e5439a3",
            "title": "Too, So, And Enough",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "There was ........................ much work to do.",
                    "description": "Note the pattern too...to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so",
                        "enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was ....................... much work that I got hardly any rest.",
                    "description": "Note the pattern so...that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "enough",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If the water is warm ........................, we may go for a swim.",
                    "description": "When enough is used as an adverb, it goes after the adjective or adverb modified by it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "enough",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The room is ........................ cold. Should I put the heating on?",
                    "description": "Too and so are possible here. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so",
                        "enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I didn't buy the coat because it was .........................",
                    "description": "Too shows undesirable extremes. Enough indicates sufficiency. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "too expensive",
                        "expensive enough",
                        "enough expensive"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We haven't got ........................ chairs.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too big",
                        "big enough",
                        "so big"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The bag was ........................ heavy that I couldn't lift it.",
                    "description": "Note the pattern so...that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "enough",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He isn't ........................ to be a soldier.",
                    "description": "When enough is used as an adverb, it goes after the adjective it modifies. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough tall",
                        "tall enough",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I haven't got ........................ to take a holiday.",
                    "description": "Too shows undesirable extremes. Enough has a positive meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "too much time",
                        "enough time",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The room is ........................ to accommodate ten people.",
                    "description": "Enough indicates sufficiency. Too shows undesirable extremes. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough spacious",
                        "spacious enough",
                        "too spacious"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They are ....................... to buy a car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rich enough",
                        "enough rich",
                        "too rich"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you drink .................... coffee, you won't get good sleep.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough",
                        "too",
                        "too much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}